<resources>
    <!-- Page and App Titles -->

    <string name="app_name">NASA Daily Image Viewer</string>
    <string name="title">Welcome to NASA Daily Image Viewer\n</string>
    <string name="viewAllImageTitle">Stored Images</string>
    <string name="searchImageTitle">Search Image</string>
    <string name="version">Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="dashBoardTitle">Dashboard</string>

    <!--Login Page -->

    <string name="emailPrompt">Enter your email address:</string>
    <string name="emailHint">Type email here</string>
    <string name="passwordPrompt">Type your password:</string>
    <string name="savePasswordCheck">Save Password</string>
    <string name="loginButton">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="helpLogin">Welcome to the login screen.  On a fresh install, a toast message will appear.
        It will tell you to enter your email and a password to setup the login.
        Unless you reinstall, this prompt will not appear again.  Enter an email address and password.
        The app stores this information for you protecting your photos with your credentials.
        There is a checkbox to prepopulate your password each time you login.  You must set this each login.\n\n

        Email:  Enter your email here.\n
        Password: Enter your password here.\n
        Login Button: Logs in.\n
        Save Password: Password field saves for next login.</string>

    <!--DashBoard Page -->

    <string name="goSearchPage">Search New Image</string>
    <string name="goViewImagePage">See All Images</string>
    <string name="goHome">Homepage</string>
    <string name="totalPhotos">Total stored photos: </string>
    <string name="lastLogin">Last Login:\n</string>
    <string name="enterAPIKey">Your API Key:\n</string>
    <string name="setAPIKey">Set Key</string>
    <string name="apiKeySet">Your API key has been set.</string>
    <string name="helpDashboard">Welcome to the dashboard.  On this page you will see information about your current app.
        It shows how many images you have stored, when you last logged in, and your API key.
        The API key can be edited by entering a new one.  If you leave the key blank, it will default to the school key.
        After you click on the \'SET Key\' button, it will set your new key.  You can navigate away with the navigation drawer menu.\n

        \nAPI key field:  Enter key here.
        </string>

    <!--SearchImage Page -->

    <string name="datePick">Choose the Date</string>
    <string name="searchImageButton">Search Image</string>
    <string name="saveImageButton">Save Image</string>
    <string name="pickerTitle">Choose The Image Date</string>
    <string name="searchImageResult">Your Image Result</string>
    <string name="dateOutRange">Please pick a new date.</string>
    <string name="dateRangeFuture">Your Date is in The Future</string>
    <string name="dateRangePast">Your Date is Too Old</string>
    <string name="dateRangeVideo">Your Date is a Video</string>
    <string name="helpSearchImage">Welcome to the search page.  This page allows you to search for a new daily image.
        You simple need to click on the \'Search Image\' button and a calendar will appear.  Choose the date
        you would like to select, and click ok.  The page will automatically download the appropriate image
        for the date selected.  If you select a date in the future, before they began image of the day, or
        a date where there is a video instead of an image, it will give you an error message.
        Once the information has been displayed, you can select the \'Save Image\' button to save, the \'Search Image\'
        button to select a new date, click on the HDURL to open the browser and see new image,
        or you can navigate away with the navigation drawer menu.
     </string>

    <!--ViewAllImage Page-->

    <string name="helpViewAllImage">Welcome to the stored images page.  On this page, you will be able to view
        all your saved images in a list.  The photo is displayed with the title underneath.  If you click on the photo,
        it will open a new window or frame if you are using a tablet, and display the image with its title, date, explanation,
        regular URL, and the HDURL.  If you click on the HDURL it will take you to your browser and load the HD image.  Simply
        click your back arrow if you want to close the new window and return to your list.  If you push and hold the photo in
        the list, it will give you an option to delete the photo from your app.  You can navigate away with the navigation drawer menu.
    </string>

    <!--Image Fragment -->

    <string name="imageDate">\nDate:</string>
    <string name="imageTitle"></string>
    <string name="imageExplanation">\nExplanation:\n</string>
    <string name="imageURL">\nURL:</string>
    <string name="imageHdURL">\nHD URL:</string>
    <string name="hideButton">HIDE</string>

    <!-- Navigation -->

    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <!-- MultiUse -->

    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="helpAlert">Help</string>


</resources>